I am Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 24.
As I announced the other day,
I will be leaving Morning Musume,
I have decided to graduate from Morning Musume。 and Hello Project after this year's fall tour.
I joined Morning Musume。 I joined Morning Musume,
I was 14 years old and from Miyagi Prefecture, and I tried to audition,
At that time, I wanted to stand out and be on a big stage,
I wanted to stand out and be on a big stage, and that's how I became a member of Morning Musume。 I wanted to stand out and be on a big stage, and that's how I became a member of Morning Musume,
I have been running up to this point with the same passion,
I have been running with the same passion for this long,
I have been having a lot of fun in the past 13 years,
I have come to love things so much,
I have come to love things so much and enjoy myself so much,
It was a discovery of a lifetime for me.
That's how I came to enjoy Morning Musume。 I think it is the right time for me to move on,
I have made up my mind that it is the right time for me to move on.
I have come to enjoy my activities as a member of Morning Musume。 I am now able to enjoy my activities as a member of Morning Musume,
I am able to enjoy my activities as a member of Morning Musume。
And also, I would like to thank all the members who are working with me,
I am grateful for all the members who are working together with me,
who give us so much strength,
I would like to thank all the members who work with us, the team members who give us so much power, and all the people who surround us. I would like to thank all the team members who support Morning Musume,
I can say that I am happy now because of the power of these people,
I am able to say that I am happy now.
Thank you very much.
Although I have decided to graduate,
I have decided to graduate, but for the remaining six months of the year,
I will work harder and harder to get more and more jobs,
I will work harder and harder for the jobs that come my way,
I would like to do that job as well,
I want to graduate with the fulfillment of all my dreams,
Please watch over me until I graduate,
Please watch over me until I graduate.
Please watch over me until I graduate from Morning Musume。 Ayumi Ishida as Morning Musume,
Please enjoy yourself.
I will enjoy it too.
Please support me until the end. Please support us to the end.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
Hello! Stay, this time with Saya Eguchi of BeyondZ Subway and Minami Okamura of BeyondZ Rain
Minami Okamura from BeyondZ Rain Morikawa Umi!
This time, we'll be bringing you a show with these two, so please stay with us until the end!
So, this is BeyondZ's new single
High to Diamond Go City Go Hook's Law
released today, May 29th!
Thank you very much.
This single is a collection of songs with different atmospheres.
I think this single has BeyondZ's style in common among them.
The standard edition also includes an additional track.
The standard edition also includes an additional track called “Ocantare” by Koisuru Ginga Worker.
Koisuru Ginga Worker's song “O Cantare” is included in this album.
It was first performed at Biophonic.
It's been over a year since it was first performed.
It's been over a year since it was first performed at Biophonic.
And what kind of music do you have in store for us?
Well, this song is about
The theme of this song is “If BeyondZ were a female office worker
The way of singing and the direction of the song has a very mature atmosphere.
I think the direction of the song was very mature.
I think that the direction of the song was very mature.
In the past BeyondZ songs, there were a lot of unison parts in the song.
But this song has solo parts for each member and
This song has solo parts for each singer, or two or three groups of singers singing together.
This song has a lot of solo parts for each singer and a lot of singing by 2 or 3 groups.
I think this song shows how cool we are by utilizing the characteristics of each voice.
And Ocantare?
Honoka Kobayashi's piano performance
The song is sung in a dozen different ways with Honoka Kobayashi's piano playing.
BeyondZ has recently been singing in a more “hamorii” or “double first melody” style.
But this time, too, they are singing in such a way in “Ocantare”.
It's really a magnificent song that makes you feel good just by listening to it. I hope you will listen to it as much as possible.
I hope you will listen to it a lot!
I hope you will listen to it a lot.
Now then, please take a look at this video.
Please take a look at this video.
Please take a look.
Chiba Prefecture, please receive our love!
Love, love, love.
I'd like to get to know you one more time, but...
What's your whole life story?
If I love you, I can tell you're there.
Hold me tight, I'm a little embarrassed
I'm so busy that I'm going around the world
I love this stage at both ends without knowing it
How many people have we passed in front of Estra et al.
I wonder how many people I've passed in front of Estra et al.
Listen to me, the age of tender love
Women and men all cheat
before they leave their mark on history
I have to come out tomorrow
I love you so much, I love you so much
Let's ride on, after all, it's a love lull
The earth and the spinning universe
Dance, dance, dance, ride it out
Big love reflection
4.6 billion years beyond love
I am a dream
Love
All right!
Oh, no!
Love.
Oh no!
Thank you
Love
Ei!
LOVELOVE
LOVE
If we could survive
Where is the place where we breathe?
Midnight is so lonely
I'm afraid to go to bed early
Everyone has a different hat once
If you don't know what's going on, you're right, it's a big fine.
If you get hurt, tell them you're hurt
I wish I could tell you that I'm hurt
It's the age of superior love that makes
It's the only way to make it, really it's the only way
I don't have to be the person I dreamed of being
I'll live my life as it was
Once in this day and age
Let's go for a ride!
In the end, it's all about the lovebirds
Earth's world and the universe
Step by step we ride on!
The big lovebread
Love transcends 4.6 billion years
Labrylid
Love Exceeds 4.6 Billion Years
Thank you for watching!
It doesn't matter if someone else has ceased to exist
Even if you're not the person you dreamed of being
I will live exactly as I live
Just for now last
Go, go, go, go!
In the end, it's all about love reflection
And the universe that covers the earth
Ride the whole line Go!
The big rublession The Big Love Recession
Love is more than 4.6 billion years
Love!
Let's go, everyone!
Oh!
Love!
Seino!
Thank you very much!
Good luck at school today!
Student Eguchi of Beyones Subway
Minami Okamura of Beyones Rainy Morikawa Sea presents Haloste.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer them at a quick pace.
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Beauty Phonic 2 will be held in Tokyo in April and in Kobe in May. If I had to sum up in one word what Beauty Phonic means to you, Minami, it would be...
A space that makes you too happy. What's the cute point of today's fashion?
I'm too excited about the summer.
When I'm in front of my fans, a mysterious energy arises.
I've been thinking a lot about the culture of the 90's teenagers.
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm usually...
I usually like to sleep all the time, and I like to be in a daze all the time.
And I'm not very athletic, so I walk very slowly and I get tired very quickly, which has been my problem lately.
But for some reason, when I go to a concert or meet with my fans, my stamina is always at a standstill.
Why do I always have such a large number of meetings?
Why do I always have so many meetings?
Why do we always have so many meetings? Why do we always have so many meetings?
I'm not sure how I'm able to live when I'm so out of breath.
I've been watching a lot of movies from the '90s, and when I watch school movies from the '90s, I'm always fascinated by the music and the rock music.
I like rock music very much, and I've always liked rock music very much.
I like rock music a lot, so when I see movies like Love Rice, it's like raggedy music or something.
And when I see things like Love Rice, it's like raggedy music.
The atmosphere of all those fashions and music is tractl migration
I feel that all the atmosphere of fashion and music is like ear
message
No matter how battered and bruised you are No matter how battered and bruised you are
I do diamond
Mira Mira
Beyond
I do diamond
Now on sale
Go city
Beyond
Now on sale
Gold Medal Power Up
Let's unleash it
Let's go
Beyond
Be yourself
Also.
BEYOND'S HOOK law NOW ON SAYA!
HELLO! STE.
Next, I would like to ask you a question, Saya-chan!
Yes, please do.
A while ago, you performed at JAPAN JAMA 2024
How did you feel about your first outdoor rock festival? How did you feel about your first outdoor rock festival?
It was great fun!
Current Spring Tour
Please write down the highlights of the current spring tour in the form of willow willow!
Spring tour that explodes with the members' individuality!
What was the moment you got burned out recently?
The moment when the live concert was over
I felt burnt out.
What's the best sweet you've had recently?
A cup full of strawberries
It was so good that I poured melted chocolate over it.
What if you perform at the end of August?
I would like to perform at the end of August for my 21st birthday and the 5th anniversary of BEYOND's major debut.
What do you want to prepare for the 5th anniversary of BEYOND's major label debut?
Improve my skills!
Thank you very much.
Aren't you too good at Chiryu Kawashima?
I was a little surprised.
I mean, I have a part in Go City Go where I say some of my thoughts on the show.
Whenever I talk about new songs lately...
I'm asked to make a Sennryu for you.
I've been asked to do that a lot.
I've been asked to do more and more.
You've improved, haven't you?
That's right.
I had to prepare for it.
Senryu came again this time.
Just in time.
No, it was wonderful!
It was as it should be.
The members' personalities exploded
As the title “personalities” suggests
As the title “Personality” suggests, this spring tour is full of each member's individuality and charm.
This spring tour is filled with each member's personality and charm, so if you haven't seen us yet, please do so.
If you haven't been to the venue yet, please come and see us.
If you haven't come to the venue yet, I hope you'll come and see us.
Please come and see us!Please.
And then...
Yes, sir.
Um...
I'm 21 years old and it's the 5th anniversary of my major label debut.
I'm preparing for this year to improve my skills.
Yes, that's right.
It sounds like there's more to it than that.
No, that's exactly what I mean.
The members of BEYOND
can do even more? It's like...
It's true.
It's like they have special skills or something.
There are many times when I feel that each member
There are many times when I feel each member is really growing up.
It's also the 5th anniversary of BEYOND's major label debut and the 6th anniversary of our company.
It's also the 6th anniversary of BEYOND's major label debut.
I hope I can be of some help to BEYOND.
I hope I can find something that can add an accent to BEYOND.
I hope to find something that I can add to BEYOND.
I would like to improve my skills and always work on my live performances.
I'm always working on my live performances with the feeling that I want to improve my skills.
I'd like to continue to work hard toward the 5th anniversary.
I'm really looking forward to seeing you in the future, Sayu-chan.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Stay tuned for more after this.
Ending
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi!
Here we are at Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have a member here.
I'm Saori Onoda from Tsubaki Factory.
I don't usually cook, so I'd like to have fun while cooking.
I'll do my best.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
So, what did you make this time?
Today I'd like to make dumplings. Today I want to make dumplings!
How do you like dumplings?
I love gyoza very much, and I have a particular favorite.
I like Hamamatsu gyoza.
They're famous where I'm from.
So I have a lot to do with gyoza.
I myself don't usually cook.
I'm a little clumsy, so I don't cook much.
I'm a little nervous today.
I'll try my best to cook in my own way.
Let's do our best!
I'll do my best.
Let's get started.
Okay, teacher, what should we do first?
First, the cabbage.
Oh, cabbage!
Cut into chunks
Chop, chop, chop.
How about a knife?
I don't usually cook, but do you have a whack knife?
Please let me know if there are any differences in the way you use them.
I haven't seen a cutting board or knife in a long time.
It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, it's been a while.
First of all, make it thin.
Yes, sir.
Long time? How long has it been?
Maybe a little thinner.
But it's okay, right?
But I'm fine.
Clumsy.
I'm going to slice it off at the end anyway.
You're right, it's getting a little thicker.
I don't know why.
It's getting bigger and bigger.
Is that right? Is this correct?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, then.
Before... before.
A little bit.
Just a little bit over there.
First of all, just go over there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a bit sharp, isn't it?
Yes, it does.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It makes you feel like you're doing it.
It makes me feel like I'm doing it.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Oh, wow.
It's much more detailed.
Thanks to you, too.
Much finer.
But it's okay if it's a little rough, right?
Yes, it's fine.
It feels good.
And this cabbage...
This cabbage here...
Salt and lentil and parsley.
All over.
I want to put it all over.
Then mix it with your hands so that it is well blended.
Yes, sir.
I leave it like this for 10 to 20 minutes.
Okay.
Hold the bottom of the bowl.
Mmm-hmm.
Now, I'm going to put some salt on this ground meat.
I'm going to put salt on it and mix it a little bit.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Yes, here.
Miyamizupalace water
Pattern
create a sticky situation
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow.
I don't know what “stickiness” means.
Make it sticky.
Have you ever seen hamburger patties kneaded?
Yes, I have.
It's just like that.
If you don't knead it well, it will fall apart.
The bean paste won't set properly.
If you put it all in and then salt it, it won't hold together.
The salt will get into the vegetables and it won't hold together.
Knead well when you only use meat.
For the minced meat, I started with just the meat and added salt.
I added salt.
I think I can talk while I'm mixing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Tsubaki will be performing at the Budokan soon.
Yes, on June 10th, at the Nippon Budokan.
This will be Sora Ninumaki's graduation performance.
Yes, it's going to be a very exciting concert.
It's going to be a very exciting concert.
Yes, it's going to be...
It's going to be.
Of course, there will be Sora Ninumaki's graduation.
And for the three new members, it's their first time performing at the Nippon Budokan.
That's great!
And in addition, we're going to have guests.
I see.
Can I tell you?
It's out, it's out.
Yes, they're here.
Riko Yamagishi, Risa Ogata.
Wow, wow, wow!
Two Yumeno Kishimoto and Taka Asakura!Two girls, Yumeno Kishimoto and Takaki Asakura.
What a lineup!
That's right, all the members of Spectraly are here!
That's amazing!
Yes, I'm sure this will be the first and last time.
I'm sure this will be the first and last time we'll be able to hold an event that will bring back some very precious memories.
I'm going to cry.
It's going to be a show that says, “Yes, that's right.
We haven't started rehearsals yet, so I don't know how it's going to be.
There are so many things to look forward to.
That's for sure.
I'm not sure what's going to happen.
I think the audience will feel the same way as we do.
I'd like to have fun while keeping myself in check.
I'm looking forward to it.
So, it's all set.
Yay!
It's completely different from the first time, isn't it?
That's for sure.
It feels firm to the touch, doesn't it?
Yes.
That's great cohesion.
The proteins have been properly broken down.
Yes, it's great.
It's looking good.
I'm going to let this rest in the fridge.
Yes, sir.
Now, while the minced meat is resting, I'll cut the chives.
If it's too big, the chives might come out.
Okay, I'll do my best.
Good, good.
I'll have to be thinner than I thought.
Yes, you're right. They cut it very carefully.
But I think it'll be easier to eat.
Yes, it is.
How do you like it?
I think it's good.I think it's good.
Looks good.
I was thinking of putting cheese in my dumplings today.
Wow, looks good.
This mosalera cheese. It's good.
I see.
It's hard to stretch when heated, so it has a nice texture.
And it goes really well with it... for cutting.
Wow, it's delicious.
One whole piece is too big, so let's cut it in half.
Yes, I understand.
It's ready.
Yes, sir.
How about this?
How is it?
It's perfect.
All right.
Let's keep the momentum going.
This is perfect.
I should have cut this first.
And the cabbage.
I think we've made it a full circle.
If we can just get it up to the next level...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My hometown is famous for dumplings.
That's right. It's famous for dumplings.
I've eaten a lot of gyoza.
But I haven't had a chance to make them.
That's because when you eat them in your hometown...
Yes.
Does your mother make them for you?
Yes, she does.
I have a definition.
Yes.
Hamamatsu gyoza must be made by someone who's lived in Hamamatsu for at least three years.
Oh, you have to be.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
And also, there's the fact that the dumplings were made in Hamamatsu.
Not the filling?
Well, there are some characteristics to what's inside.
But that's the definition.
That they are made in Hamamatsu.
Yes.
So, if your parents made it for you...
That's Hamamatsu gyoza.
Ah...
Then you can't make them yourself.
That's right.
It's been a long time.
I'm done.
Yes, sir.
Now, let's take this cabbage. Cabbage. It's been a long time, and the water hasn't come out much.
It doesn't look like much water has come out, but let's tap it with a piece of paper
It looks a little more cohesive.
Let's put it in like this and mix it.
I've never done this process before. Isn't it fun?
It's hard to mix because it's sticky.
This is the proof that it's sticky. Let's add seasonings.
A teaspoon of sugar.
1 teaspoon sesame oil. 1 gram salt.
1 teaspoon miso.
This is the secret ingredient.
Miso. It's rare to put miso in.
Then mix in some vegetables.
Add chives, too.
Gyoza with atmosphere.
At once! The filling is full of vegetables!
It's good. And... if you let it rest in the fridge...
If you let them rest in the fridge, they'll get a little firmer and easier to handle.
That's all for this time. That's all for this time.
Next time we'll wrap them up and make delicious dumplings.
Let's do our best. I'll do my best. Thank you very much.
The first one. My first dumpling. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let me see, let me see, let me see. Let me see for the camera, let me see for the camera.
How's it going? No, no, no, no.
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolutely.
Yeah. Wow. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow, yummy.
Halo! Halo!
This is Kisora Shinnuma from Tsubaki Factory.
We will be performing “Camon Everybody” with new members, Miu Ishii and Yu Murata, at the “Ready to Go Now” special for Kisora Niinuma's graduation.
This time, I participated in the lesson, so please take a look at the performance!
Hey, everyone, let's take a look!
Is today the day to learn the song?
I was wondering if it was a day to learn how to sing too.
I thought so when I looked at the schedule.
Maybe I was too focused on learning to dance.
I was probably too preoccupied with learning how to dance.
I thought it was a one-time-only event, so when you perform at the Nippon Budokan, you don't have to do it as many times as you do now.
It's not a place where you can grow and develop like you can on the current tour.
It's not a place where you can grow and develop.
I need to practice and move my mouth properly.
I thought about it a little bit.
And there were some details that I thought were a little different
I thought there were some details that weren't quite right.
I'd like to fix that.
Yes, please.
It's not so jumpy.
This song is a very cute song, but it's also a very difficult song to play rhythmically.
but it's also a very difficult song in terms of rhythm.
Especially in the chorus part, there are a lot of unison
It is very difficult to keep the rhythm while singing
It's very difficult to keep the rhythm while singing.
There are a lot of steps in this song.
I remember the first time I choreographed this song
I remember that I had a hard time with the foot steps when I choreographed this song for the first time.
That's how much the charlestone step in the chorus isThat's how much the charlestone step in the chorus foot is.
If you are a member who has never danced before, you should be able to do it from the very beginning.
It's very difficult for them to be able to do it from the beginning.
It's very difficult for them to be able to do it.
So I could see that the three of them had practiced this step very hard in the lesson.
I was thinking of using this face here and there.
I'm now thinking that it would be better to use various facial expressions...
Okay, okay, okay.
These hairs are pretty cute.
I think it's important to make it cute.
This clap is also pretty sideways.
I thought it might make Miu's rhythm a little off.
Miu-chan is probably going to learn from me on this lesson day.
I wondered if she had memorized all my choreography.
I felt a lot of love from that.
Miu-chan is very quick to absorb what she learns from me, so I wondered how she would feel in the next lesson.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how she will be at the next lesson.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how you will be in the next lesson.
I had the impression that she changed her hand gestures for each performance during the spring tour.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how you will perform on the day of the show.
Can I ask you a question?
I think Yoo-chan is a girl who is very passionate about her performance.
She is a really good dancer, so I think she will lead Tsubaki Factory in the future in terms of dance.
I think Yoo-chan's challenge is to balance dancing and singing at the same time.
I'm looking forward to seeing how much she can improve her skills during the rehearsal period before the performance.
And then there's Fuuka Doi.
I feel that Fuuka-chan is very similar to my trainee days.
I think she's doing her best and listening to what I'm saying, but
But I felt that she would get impatient and anxious when she tried to do it.
But she's usually so bright and cheerful, and she's so cute, like the youngest child in the family.
I wonder if that feeling will shine through when she is on stage.
I think the key point is how she shines when she is on stage.
And after the dance lesson is over
They are practicing singing and dancing with a microphone.
They did their best to memorize the lyrics for the lesson.
But to be honest, I'm not sure if I'm ready yet.
During the rehearsal period of the spring tour, I will try my best to teach them what I can.
I would like to do my best to bring out the best of Sunry during the rehearsal period of the spring tour.I wanted to do my best to bring out the best in Sunley.
I'm not very good at using my feet in Charleston.
I tend to move too big or too small.
The pauses were difficult, so I wanted to make them just right.
I wanted to get the timing just right.
We had done trials before, so we practiced a lot this time, too.
So this time, I would like to show you a solid performance by the three of us after a lot of practice.
I think it's really difficult to practice for a performance.
When you are conscious of one thing, you lose one thing.
That's what I thought was difficult.
Shinnuma-san told me that I should make the “Uruwashi no chamelia” prettier.
I tried to dance and express myself in a way that matched the concept of the performance.
I want to do it with a cute expression and a smile on my face, and I want to make sure that the angle of my hands are cute.
The rhythm of the song is very detailed in my mind, and it's very difficult to get the rhythm right, so I'll do my best to keep the rhythm when I sing and dance.
I will only have one lecture at the Budokan, so I will make the most of that one lecture and review what I have learned today and make it perfect before the next lesson.
I want to do my best so that the audience can see us even on that night.
I can't wait to see how the three of us will shine at the Nippon Budokan.
And how will they show their freshness that they can only show now?
I myself am really looking forward to it!
I'm really happy to be able to sing and dance at the Nippon Budokan, so I'm sure it will be a great experience for the three of us.
I think it will be a great experience for the three of us.
I hope they will lead Tsubaki Factory from now on.
I wish you all the best!
Seino
I'll do my best!
Please come to Nippon Budokan on June 10!
Beyond Subway Egtsuete
Beyond Rain Morikawa Umi no Okamura Minami presents Halo! Stay!
Beyond is currently holding Beyond Live Tour 2024 Spring Personality!
This tour is the last tour with the current 11 members.
Yuhane Yamazaki's graduation has been decided.
The members themselves will be watching Yuhane Yamazaki's figure and singing voice in the live performance.
This will be the first live house tour for the members themselves.
I'm really fired up about this tour and I'm feeling a sense of distance with the audience that I've never felt before.
We are also looking forward to the close proximity to the audience that we have never had before.
We are enjoying the close proximity to the audience and the passionate atmosphere of the tour.
From the spring tour, we will be performing a new song that was released today, “GO!
CITY GO! You will see a live video of GO!CITY GO!
CITY GO!
This song is a collaboration with JR Tokai.
The name of all the stations on the Tokaido Shinkansen line are in the song.
Also, the music video was shot on the Shinkansen.
And the music video was shot while we were all traveling together on the Shinkansen.
I think it's a very cute song.
And one thing I've been thinking about recently...
This song is more live than the music video or the soundtrack.
This song was performed live before the music video or the soundtrack was released to the public.
As I mentioned earlier, the song goes along with the rhythm of “GO!
CITY GO!
There were a few moments in the first few shows
But that's what a live house tour is all about.
I was so close to the audience that I couldn't hear them.
During the MC at the Prime Minister's office
I thought it would be fun to call out with this kind of rhythm.
I thought about it with the members and the audience, and we came up with the chorus.
In the preparation stage of recording and choreographing, we found a new fun that we didn't feel much at the beginning.
I discovered a new sense of fun that I hadn't felt much during the preparation stage of recording and choreographing.
I was very happy to discover a new kind of fun that I didn't feel when I was preparing for the recording and choreography.
And this song has many elements...
Saya!
Isn't there a point of interest?
Yes, I do.
In the interlude part of this song, I'm performing a “willow”.
Shin-Osaka is the name of a willow tree in Osaka.
I intonate a little bit in the Kansai dialect.
I hope you will pay attention to it at the live performance.
Please have a look!
Music
Go! City! Go!
Go! City! Go! City! Go! City!
Go! City! Go! City! Go! City! Go! City!
After the shoes that make noise and jump into love
Staring at the place, knowing no loss
Who's fault is it when it's time to be dead?
I'll twist a phrase, I'll think of it, I'll think of it
Near Tokyo, Shinagawa area
Hey, everywhere
Shin-Yokohama, Odawara, Atami
Shizuoka
Shizuoka.
Be with you
From Paradise
Ah
Regret, my former name is running through
I couldn't wait, so like me, spring up
Go, city, go There's so many things I want to tell you
I wonder if there's a song I'll be excited to sing
Go city, go you, go you, go you, go you, go city, go city
Go city, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, go you, city.
I've got a view, a body that dances better than the rain
Kochi, live in spring, summer, fall, winter
Koukou ni mo mo mo mo mo happy natsuyasumi
Travel, and expand your world
Mishima Takeda Bay Toyohashi Nagoya
Let's go!
Mikawa Anjo In the name of the river
Stay my one love
There's so many cities I want to play in
In the back of my chest, behind the barrel, in this town
Light floods in from the car window, on my knees
My husband and I are held together by our precious drumming
No one's enough, I want to see you right now
Go, Chippy Girl!
Go! Chippy Girl!
Shinfuji Hamamatsu
Carry Bag, Pattern Time, Spring, Shin-Osaka, Jiyori Carry Bag Patterned Spring Going Shin-Osaka Jiyori
Wow!
Japan
Go! City! Go! Life!
Running through the Tokai region
Is it me who is not popular?
Spring is coming early!
Hello, I have so many things I want to tell you
I'm excited because there's a song
Go!
Go, city, go, siddie, go, siddie, go, go, siddie, go, go, siddie, go, siddie, go, siddie, go, siddie, go, siddie
SIDDIE GO! SIDDIE GO! SIDDIE SIDDIE!
GO! SIDDY GO!
We're always here for you! Go!
Beyond Subway Egtsuetto
Beyond Rainy Morikawa Umi no Okamura Minami presents Haloste.
It's time to say goodbye!
Here's an announcement!
Beyond's 5th single
High to Diamond Go!
Hook's Law was released today!
City Go!
City Go!” is a collaboration with JR Tokai.
City Go! City Go!” is a collaboration song with JR Tokai, and the campaign has started today!
You can listen to Beyond's voice only in the Shinkansen and there is a stamp rally.
We hope you will enjoy the project as well as the trip!
And we, Beyond, are going to
Beyond Live Tour 2024 Spring Personality
As the title says, this tour is a tour that makes full use of our personalities.
Next stop will be Hokkaido, so please come and visit us!
Please come and visit us!
And on June 27th, Beyond Live Tour 2024 Spring Personality Wings of Dreams will be held!
It will be the graduation performance of Yuhane Yamazaki, a member of the group, and the final show of the tour.
It will be the last performance with 11 members.
We hope to make it a fun performance full of smiles.
Please check it out!
And to celebrate the 1000th broadcast of Pretty Cure, we, Beyond, are going to participate in the ending dance of the show.
We are participating in the ending dance of Pretty Cure!We are participating in the ending dance of Pretty Cure!
The video will be distributed on the official YouTube channel of Pretty Cure
Please check it out!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will appear more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
This time we are joined by Masato Eguchi of Beyond Subway
Minami Okamura of Beyond Rain Morikawa Umi
Good bye.